
    ^  ^
   /¯¯¯¯\
  < Ο  O >
   \    /
  /¯\▄▄/¯\ 
 / / '' \ \
 WW /¯¯\ Ww
  ||    ||
  \|    |/
  | \__/ |
  |W|  |W|
Update: 10/30/04 - 

New Kung-fu idle animation, by Yarby.


   ¯    ¯
Badger.

Badger Badger Badger, no mushrooms.

Original model by the talented and helpfull -Rachel Cordone-. Originally done for Unreal tournament 2003, 
i'd not have been able to do anything without her compliance. Sorry it's taken so long, frankly I didn't have 
any idea what I was doing..

Assigng to TS default skeleton, slight modification, slight bit of animating, Done by me, the mystery author 
of this readme.

Readme by Kit the fox.

To use this, extract the files from the zip file, and make sure "use folder paths" or something similar is checked off. 

The model should then be installed.

Once in game, use the console to choose your model. Type "model badger", or "model Rbadger" for the realistic 
version. You can use other ways to pick installed models, be sure to experiment with them all.

If in doubt, follow this link. It will explain things in painfull detail.

http://specialistscentral.com/forums/index.php?act=ST&f=10&t=4938&


      /*
   .-^  |
 q~ n   `.. - - - - - .
  ',~~\                `.
      `.   }    {    /\  '.
        \  |~- -~\   | \   m.
        || |     >> /   '.mmm.    
 \\|/   m|m|    m/m/      '''   ||/
                     \|//

